#### Augita Yasmin

Klender • Jakarta, 13470 • augitayasmin@gmail.com • 089607123166 • Linkedln : Augita Yasmin • https://augitayasmin.netlify.app/

#### **Summary**

A third-year graduated of Telecommunication student from Politeknik Negeri Jakarta who are a hard worker person, agile, flexible, good at time management, responsible, easy to adapt to new things, and can work individually or in a team. My last project (thesis) was designing hardware based on Internet of Things using Arduino IDE for microcontroller program and designing user interface for the software using Figma. So I am experienced in making real-time database, troubleshooting microcontroller things, networking, designing PCB, topology, user interface, etc. Now, highly interested on UI/UX design and still learning forward in that field.

## **Education**

## Politeknik Negeri Jakarta

Depok

Diploma Degree of Telecommunication, Electrical Engineering. GPA: 3.35

2019 - 2022

Thesis: Rancang Bangun Sistem Pendeteksi Asap Rokok Tembakau dan Uap Rokok Elektrik di Kamar Hotel berbasis Internet of Things dan Aplikasi Android |

URL = https://drive.google.com/file/d/1uNOHpcJY8DkdmJG9hFNuAsMzUYHeCAGA/view?usp=sharing Relevant Coursework:

- Cyber Security "A Specialist's Sight: Monitoring Attacks and Cyber Threat Hunting" by A Renewal Agent (2021)
- Internet of Things "Peran IoT dalam Persiapan Menuju Indonesia Emas 2045" by A Renewal Agent (2021)
- Kuliah Tamu Elektro by Universitas Hang Tuah Surabaya (2021)
- TERESTRIAL "Telecommunication Ready for Evolution of Industrial 4.0" by Politeknik Negeri Jakarta (2020)

#### Other Coursework:

- Fullstack Intensive Bootcamp UI/UX Design by MySkill.id (2022)
- Digital Festival UI/UX Design by Rakamin (2022)
- Strategy of Product Management by Kelas.work (2022)
- Belajar Desain UI dan UX Website dari Pemula sampai Mahir by Arkademi (2022)
- Fundamental Digital Marketing by Eduwork (2022)
- Creating an Entrepreneurial Evolution with Marketing Techniques and Digital Markets by Self Development Program (2021)
- Media Sosial Untuk Usaha Anda by A Grow With Google Program (2021)

### **Experience**

Self Project

**African Grev** 

Oct 2022 - Present

Web Designer | URL = https://www.figma.com/proto/WVkPws3X6lMFlAwTjcnfkN/ciwis?nodeid=1%3A2&scaling=scale-down&page-id=0%3A1&starting-point-node-id=1%3A2

• Designing responsive website for knowledge about African Grey Parrot.

Self Project Sep 2022 – Oct 2022

### Nyummyl

Web Designer | URL = <a href="https://nyummyl.netlify.app/">https://nyummyl.netlify.app/</a>

• Designing responsive website for my own business that sold many variant of cookies.

#### Augita Yasmin

Self Project

**Tokopaedi** Sep 2022 – Present

Web Designer | URL = <a href="https://www.figma.com/proto/SOKbBAzu7Htd0Y29NkDLro/tokopaedi?node-id=60%3A504&scaling=scale-down&page-id=60%3A81&starting-point-node-id=60%3A504">https://www.figma.com/proto/SOKbBAzu7Htd0Y29NkDLro/tokopaedi?node-id=60%3A504&scaling=scale-down&page-id=60%3A81&starting-point-node-id=60%3A504</a>

• Designing responsive website for e-commerce purposes.

SWeather Self Project

Web Designer | URL = <a href="https://nyusweather1.netlify.app/">https://nyusweather1.netlify.app/</a>

Aug 2022 – Sep 2022

• Designing responsive website for weather detector based on its device location.

NYUNYU'S MART Self Project

Web Designer | URL = https://nyunyumart.netlify.app/

Jul 2022 – Aug 2022

• Designing responsive website for notes maker of groceries reminder.

# **Information Technology Infrastructure Engineer**

PT. Perusahaan Pengelola Aset

Aug 2021 – Nov 2021

Internship

- Designing a topology network (tree topology) at 7<sup>th</sup>, 8<sup>th</sup>, and 9<sup>th</sup> floors.
- Do installation of Unifi devices (reset all devices then connect the router switch to client/PC, access point, internet and other router switch with LAN cable).
- Make a server in VMware for a network which give internet access for 7<sup>th</sup>, 8<sup>th</sup>, and 9<sup>th</sup> floors with enterprise system.
- Change the security on authentication from personal to enterprise system using Windows Server and Unifi web.

#### Kuliah Umum Telekomunikasi

Politeknik Negeri Jakarta

Multimedia Division

Aug 2021 – Oct 2021

Make a trophy design for two lecturers.

### Program Kreativitas Mahasiswa

Member

Politeknik Negeri Jakarta Feb 2021 – Mar 2021

• Development designing of medical purposes in monitoring of temperature and heart rate to indicate patients who are infected with the covid-19 virus based on the internet of things.

#### **Skills & Interests**

- PicsArt
- Proteus
- NI Multisim
- Eagle

Score: 580/990

- Tinkercad
- EasyEDA

- Cisco Packet Tracer
- Canva
- Figma
- Microsoft Word
- Microsoft PowerPoint
- Microsoft Excel

### **Achievements**

**TOEIC English Competency Test** 

Politeknik Negeri Jakarta Issued Jul 2022 – Jul 2023